<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Project Portafolio</title><link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Project Portafolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 23:29:21 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Credit Scoring Model</title><link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/emoji-support/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 23:29:21 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/emoji-support/</guid><description>In base of the work of Naeem Siddiqi, the author of &amp;ldquo;Credit Risk Scorecards Developing and Implementing Intelligent Credit Scoring&amp;rdquo;, we are going to propose a credit scoring model for credit cards in base of the data from the bank Interbank. The purpose of the model is to find a credit profile for each customer in order to predict the default risk od the portalio. This model is going to be elaborate using python.</description></item><item><title>Sentiment analysis of the news in the Peru: The effect on the dolar</title><link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/placeholder-text/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 23:29:21 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/blog/placeholder-text/</guid><description>In base of the last event in the politic field in Peru and in order to understand the impact of the market sentiment, we are going to create a sentiment index in base of the digital news of the newspaper &amp;ldquo;Gestión&amp;rdquo;. To extract the information we are goint to use techniques of web scrapping to extract all the data. After that construct a sentiment index in using NLP algorithms. This work is looking to know is there a correlation betweeen the market sentiments, how the market percives these in base of the lenguage present in the news and how the volatility of the dolar behave.</description></item></channel></rss>